hdwebplayer.com 2016-10-24

# Privacy Policy

#### Preface

HDW Player is an Online Video Player for your websites that allows you to display your videos instantly. We offer a video player with generous products and services that allows websites to embed video, stream videos and deliver advertising across the Internet. Our company serves for Users - surfing the web, Advertisers - advertising their products & services and Publishers - providing video & placing our products on their websites. We help our end users who place our products & services on their websites to understand how their videos are viewed and which of their ads are more effective that’s being viewed many times. Our company values your privacy & data security. We wish you to know how we collect, conceal or disclose and handle your Personal Identifiable Information (PII) & Non-Personal Identifiable Information online.

#### Privacy procedure for our Video player Technology

We may use Google Analytics to collect our User’s non-personally identifiable information such as IP address, ISP, browser type, OS of computer or mobile device, the URL of the page where our player technology is used, the referring URL, player version, duration and time of video played, any advertising message included in the video, video screen mode and metadata of Video or the web page Publisher. We use this third party analytics tool to know which page of our website is popular that made our visitors into users.

#### Privacy practices for your PII and other Information

We collect your PII such as your name, contact number, email Id and mailing address if it is required for any functions when you register to set up an account. You may need to provide your billing or payment information and credit card details when you buy or order for commercial license and package. We gather a few of your Non-Personal and demographic information such as the URL and admin details of your website which requires our service or product.

#### Usage of your PII and other Information

We get your information to understand your requirement and serve you with a better product or service. We use your information for processing your order or to reply you for any queries. Our service or product may limit customers to purchase or to get advantage of some features from our website if certain information is not provided. Periodically, we may send promotional emails and special offers to our free version users and subscribers for advising to buy the paid version if required or we think that you are interested in such offers. Moreover, we may use your information occasionally for the purpose of market research and customize our products or services.

#### Opt-out facility

We do provide an option to opt-out or unsubscribe from marketing emails if you do not want to receive. If you no longer wish to share your PII with third parties or our affiliates for marketing purposes, you may opt-out by sending us an email. If you opt out from us, we will not remove your PII from third parties or our affiliate’s database with whom we have shared your PII already. We recommend you to contact them directly to stop receiving marketing emails from such third parties or affiliates. We request you to mention whether you opt-out from sharing your data with third parties or from receiving emails from us.

#### How do we protect your Privacy

Your privacy is very important to us and we pledge to secure your privacy. We adhere with all legal Online Privacy Policy and aim to fulfill you with all applicable laws of data protection act. All your information is treated and used confidentially. Your information may be transferred to countries that may not need an adequate level of protection and retained back securely. We transmit your credit card data over an encrypted secure server connection to our payment partners and this communication is SSL-secured. We do not save your card information on our systems. We safeguard your data we collect online by suitable electronic, physical and administrative procedures to prevent disclosure and unauthorized access.

#### How do we use cookies

We use cookies on our website to understand the usage of our technology and improve user experience. Cookies are small text files that ask permission to get downloaded to your computer’s hard drive. Cookies are used by web servers to track a user’s navigation on different pages and identify their returns to a website. If you agree, it stores your login credentials, session authorization data, return URLS, while coming back from a third party site. We use both constant and session cookies that alters as per your likes, dislikes and needs by remembering data about your preferences. We do not create any personal tracking profiles and for except non-persistent site, we do not link any of your personal data to cookies. We use Flash and similar technologies for enabling our video players. We do not use Flash cookies for analytics or advertising purposes.

#### Disclosures of additional Privacy

##### Information Security

Your information security is our central focus. We use valid security procedures to protect your information both when it is received and during transmission but that is not limited to firewalls and encryption use. We protect your personal information from abuse, loss, disclosure or modification by taking all useful steps. However, no transmission method or electronic storage over the Internet is 100% secure. We cannot guarantee the complete security of information transmitted over the Internet even we try our best commercial means of security. We recommend you to protect your personal data by taking all necessary safety measures while you are online. We also advise you to avoid guessing of login credentials, disclosure or related leakage.

##### Altering or Deleting your Personally Identifiable Information

At any time you may modify, update, delete or deactivate your PII that you have entered on our website. We are just an email away to change your data; you may send your request to admin@hdwplayer.com for avoiding any invalid action. Our company will process your request after completing few procedures within a specific period of time. Note that your request might terminate our HDW Player service and cause issues with purchase and license verification. If you have forgotten your username or password you can retrieve it safely with a simple step. We request you to inform us about any changes or errors in your PII and help us in keeping your accurate records.

##### Children Related information

Our website and services or products are designed only for persons with 13 years of age and above. We request children under the age of 13, not to enter any of your PII in the site. Please contact us to remove any PII information if we collect by mistake from your child.

#### Disclosure to Third Parties

HDW Player does not disclose, share, rent or sell your personal information to any person without your approval, except to mention in this section.

  1. If you inform us that you want to share your PII with our trusted third parties which you may find interesting, our company may share with those we are authorized and prohibit them from using your information for any purpose other than performing HDW Player service.
  2. We may share your PII if it is required by law to do so, to take action with respect to any violation of law or any supposed violation of the Terms of Service, to government financial authorities, for investigation and threats to the safety of a person.
  3. We may transfer or disclose your personal information to our related entities or affiliates, with a corporate merger, bankruptcy, consolidation and other change for the above reasons. Sale of assets to a third party or change in ownership will be notified via notice on our website.
  4. Our company may disclose your personal information to our employees and to any third parties hired to perform back-end services or our website associated functions. Such third parties adhere to comply with our obligations as under our Terms of Service.

#### Any changes to this Privacy Policy

HDW Player may occasionally update this policy and is subject to change. If there are any essential or material changes in the way we treat your personal information, we will inform you via your primary email Id or we will post a clear notice on our website while we notify in this privacy policy.

#### Third party cookies

Third party vendors like Google AdSense, DoubleClick programs would use cookies to advertise on our website. Learn [Google ads cookies](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/technologies/ads/). Use [Advertise Settings](https://www.google.com/ads/preferences/) to manage the Google advertising and opt out of interest-based ads.

#### Measuring site visitors

We measure this website visitors through google analytics program. Learn about [Google Analytics](http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html) and [opt out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

#### Contacting us

Please contact us by email at support@hdwplayer.com with certain subject regarding any questions about this Privacy Policy. You can write, chat and call us through our Contact Us page.

Last updated: October 12, 2016
